A Guide to the Robert S. Bloxom Papers, 1978-2003
Library of Virginia
- Series II. Issue Files, 1978-2003., Extent: 45 boxes. (Box 18-62)
  - Chesapeake Bay Bridge Tunnel. (Box 21, Folder 1-4)
  - Chesapeake Bay Impact Crater. (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Children's Health 1985. (Box 21, Folder 6-7)
  - Children's Health - State Children's Health Insurance Program (SCHIP). (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Chincoteague-Accomack Settlement Agreement. (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Chincoteague Billboards. (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Chincoteague Pony Association. (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Chincoteague Refuge Center. (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Chincoteague Island Harbor Question. (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Citizens for a Better Eastern Shore. (Box 22, Folder 2-3)
  - Clam Dredging. (Box 22, Folder 4-7)
  - Coal Slurry Pipeline. (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Commercial Space Flight Authority. (Box 22, Folder 9-12)
  - Commercial Watermen. (Box 22, Folder 13-14)
  - Community Colleges - Clippings. (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Community Corrections. (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Community Services Board. (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Comparative Fault. (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Conservation and Reinvestment Act - CARA Light. (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Constituent Correspondence, March-August 2000. (Box 23, Folder 5-9)
  - Constituent Correspondence, August-December 2000. (Box 23, Folder 10-14)
  - Constituent Correspondence, August-December 2000. (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Constituents - Gloucester County. (Box 24, Folder 2-5)
  - Correspondence, 1 January - 1 August 2001. (Box 24, Folder 6-11)
  - Correspondence, 1 January - 1 August 2001. (Box 25, Folder 1-2)
  - Correspondence, 2002. (Box 25, Folder 3-11)
  - Correspondence, 1 November - 31 December 2002. (Box 25, Folder 12-13)
  - Correspondence, 1 November - 31 December 2002. (Box 26, Folder 1-2)
  - Correspondence, 2003. (Box 26, Folder 3-14)
  - Correspondence, 1 March - 31 July 2003. (Box 27, Folder 1-8)
  - Crab Study. (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Crabs. (Box 27, Folder 10-12)
  - Crabs. (Box 28, Folder 1-11)
  - Crabs. (Box 29, Folder 1-9)
  - Craney Island. (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Criminal Justice Academy. (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Criminal Justice Services. (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Deadrise Boat. (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Delmarva Conservation Corridor. (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Delmarva Fireman's Statue/Delmarva Advisory Council. (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Delmarva Intercoastal Waterway. (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Delmarva Power Rate Request. (Box 30, Folder 2-3)
  - Delmarva Rural Ministries. (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Delmarva Statehood. (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Dental Care. (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Dentist - Health Fair, 2001. (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Department of Corrections Study, 2000. (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Dillon Rule. (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Dry Fire Hydrants. (Box 30, Folder 10-14)
  - Duck Stamps. (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - Easement - Peaker Plant. (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - Eastern Shore Center for Independent Living. (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Eastern Shore Committee for Better Housing. (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Eastern Shore Community College. (Box 31, Folder 3-5)
  - Eastern Shore Community College - Student Aid. (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Eastern Shore Community College - Workforce Training Center. (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Eastern Shore Community Services Board - Hospital Beds. (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Eastern Shore Historical Society. (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Eastern Shore Music Festival. (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Eastern Shore of Virginia Regional Partnership, 22 February 1999. (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Eastern Shore of Virginia Regional Partnership, 22 March 1999. (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Eastern Shore of Virginia Regional Partnership, 26 April 1999. (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Eastern Shore of Virginia Regional Partnership Meeting, 22 January 2001. (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Eastern Shore of Virginia Regional Partnership Meeting, 28 January 2002. (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - Eastern Shore Railroad. (Box 31, Folder 16-20)
  - Eastern Shore Resource Conservation and Development Project. (Box 32, Folder 1-5)
  - Eastern Shore Rural Health. (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Eastern Shore Rural Health System. (Box 32, Folder 7-8)
  - Economic Development - Eastern Shore. (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Education Disparity. (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Eel Pots. (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Enhanced 911 Service. (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Enterprise Zones. (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Environment. (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - Exmore Grant Application. (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - Family Life Education. (Box 32, Folder 16-17)
  - Farmers - Economic Study. (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - Farmers' Market. (Box 33, Folder 1-4)
  - Farmers' Market, 1988. (Box 33, Folder 5-8)
  - Farmers' Markets. (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Federal Retirees - Harper Litigation. (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Fire Companies and EMS. (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Fire Companies and EMS. (Box 34, Folder 1-11)
  - Fishing Licenses. (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Fishing Licenses. (Box 35, Folder 1-3)
  - Flounder. (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Forestry. (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Freedom of Information Act (FOIA). (Box 35, Folder 6-7)
  - French Oyster Trip, 2000. (Box 35, Folder 8-9)
  - Gambling. (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - General Obligation Bonds. (Box 35, Folder 11-12)
  - Grievance Procedure. (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - Groundwater. (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - Groundwater - Eastern Shore. (Box 36, Folder 1-3)
  - Groundwater - Eastern Shore (Nitrogen Data). (Box Personal Papers Oversize Box 12)
  - Guns. (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Health Care/Nurses. (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Healthy Families. (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Helicopter/Medevac Services. (Box 36, Folder 7-9)
  - Historic Resources. (Box 36, Folder 10-12)
  - Hickman, Milton T.. (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Home Health Services - Eastern Shore, 1996. (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Housing. (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Hunger. (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Hunting - Duck Blinds. (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Income Tax. (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Initiative and Referendum. (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Inspector General (H.B. 1034). (Box 37, Folder 7-8)
  - Insurance. (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Insurance Liability. (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Interest on LawyerTrust Accounts (IOLTA). (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Intracoastal Waterway. (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - Jail. (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - Jobs for Virginia Graduates. (Box 37, Folder 14-15)
  - Judges. (Box 37, Folder 16-18)
  - Juvenile Correctional Center Tour. (Box 37, Folder 19)
  - Keve, Paul W.. (Box 37, Folder 20)
  - Kiptopeke State Park. (Box 38, Folder 1-5)
  - Kiptopeke State Park - Terminal Building (Architectural Drawing). (Search Barcode 0005627562) (Map-case 4, Drawer 5)
  - KMC Foods, Inc. (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Land Conservation Foundation. (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Land Conservation Workshop, 2001. (Box 38, Folder 8-9)
  - Land Gains Tax. (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Land Use. (Box 38, Folder 11-13)
  - Library - Northampton. (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - License Plates - Tourism/Pony. (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - License Revocation. (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Lottery. (Box 39, Folder 4-8)
  - Lottery - School Construction. (Box 39, Folder 9-10)
  - Liquidated Damages. (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - Management Plan for Ungranted State Lands. (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - Maps - Chesapeake Bay-Roanoke and Tangier Sounds (4 copies). (Search barcode 0005627562) (Map-case 4, Drawer 5)
  - Marine Expediters. (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - Mathews Memorial Library. (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - Mayors - Eastern Shore. (Box 39, Folder 15-17)
  - Mayors - Eastern Shore. (Box 40, Folder 1-5)
  - Medicaid Loophole. (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Medical Assistance/Health. (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Menhaden Fishing. (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Menhaden Resource Council. (Box 40, Folder 9-10)
  - Mental Health. (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Merritt, Patti. (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - Metompkin Island. (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - Mid-Chesapeake Bay Ferry. (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - Migrant Head Start Program. (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - Migrant Housing - 1988 Study. (Box 41, Folder 1-2)
  - Migrants. (Box 41, Folder 3-4)
  - Miscellaneous, 1988. (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous, 1990. (Box 41, Folder 6-7)
  - Miscellaneous, January-August 1999. (Box 41, Folder 8-12)
  - Miscellaneous, January-August 1999. (Box 42, Folder 1-6)
  - Miscellaneous, August-December 1999. (Box 42, Folder 6-11)
  - Miscellaneous, August-December 1999. (Box 43, Folder 1-2)
  - Miscellaneous, January-February 2000. (Box 43, Folder 3-12)
  - Miscellaneous, January-February 2001. (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - Miscellaneous, January-February 2001. (Box 44, Folder 1-10)
  - Miscellaneous, August-November 2001. (Box 44, Folder 11-13)
  - Miscellaneous, August-November 2001. (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous, November-December 2001. (Box 44, Folder 2-4)
  - Miscellaneous, March-June 2002. (Box 44, Folder 5-8)
  - Miscellaneous, July-November 2002. (Box 45, Folder 9-11)
  - Miscellaneous, July-November 2002. (Box 46, Folder 1-4)
  - Miscellaneous, August-December 2003. (Box 46, Folder 5-8)
  - Model General Assembly. (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - Morris Island. (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - NASA. (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - New Road Community Development Group of Exmore, Inc.. (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - No Car Tax. (Box 47, Folder 1-4)
  - No-Growth Movement. (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Non-Tidal Wetlands. (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Northampton-Accomack Memorial Hospital. (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - Northampton Leadership Forum. (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Northern Neck-Middle Peninsula Public Education Consortium. (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Offender Aid and Restoration (OAR). (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - Opthalmic Steroids. (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Outdoor Recreation. (Box 47, Folder 12-14)
  - Outdoor Recreation. (Box 48, Folder 1-8)
  - Oyster Dredging. (Box 48, Folder 9-10)
  - Oyster Harbor Project. (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - Oyster Leases. (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - Oysters. (Box 48, Folder 13-15)
  - Oysters - Sunday Fishing. (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Oysters - UVA Department of Environmental Sciences. (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Painter - Concerned Citizens for Improvements. (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Parental Notification. (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Parker's Creek/Perdue Farms. (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Pesticides. (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Pharmacy. (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - Plasticulture. (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - Plasticulture/Agriculture. (Box 49, Folder 9-11)
  - Port Authority. (Box 49, Folder 12-16)
  - Poultry Waste. (Box 50, Folder 1-5)
  - Prison - Northampton County. (Box 50, Folder 6-12)
  - Public Safety/Corrections. (Box 51, Folder 1-3)
  - Radio Press Releases, 1981. (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Rainy Day Fund/Revenue Data. (Box 51, Folder 5-6)
  - Republican Caucus Rules. (Box 51, Folder 7-8)
  - Resource Conservation and Development Council. (Box 51, Folder 9-10)
  - Resource Conservation and Development Council/Soil Conservation. (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - Resource Recovery Investment Associates - Hallwood. (Box 51, Folder 12)
  - Retirement - Federal/State. (Box 51, Folder 13)
  - Retirement - Federal/State. (Box 52, Folder 1-3)
  - Rural Venture, Inc.. (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Saltwater Fishing Licenses. (Box 52, Folder 5-9)
  - Saltwater Tax to VMRC. (Box 52, Folder 10-12)
  - Savage, Mrs. J.T.. (Box 52, Folder 13)
  - School Health. (Box 53, Folder 1-2)
  - School Health - Medicaid. (Box 53, Folder 3-4)
  - School Nursing - Medicaid. (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - School Prayer. (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - School Vouchers. (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - Seafood Market Task Force. (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - Search and Rescue. (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - Seaside Fishing Licenses. (Box 53, Folder 10)
  - Secretarial System. (Box 53, Folder 11-12)
  - Seed Potato. (Box 53, Folder 13)
  - Seed Potato Board. (Box 53, Folder 14)
  - Seed Tree Law Exemption. (Box 53, Folder 15)
  - Shad. (Box 53, Folder 16-17)
  - Shore Health Services, Inc.. (Box 53, Folder 18)
  - Shore LifeCare at Parksley. (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Small Business. (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - Social Services. (Box 54, Folder 3-4)
  - Soil Mapping. (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - Sounding Horns. (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - Southern Legislative Conference. (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - Space Port - Wallops. (Box 54, Folder 8-10)
  - Special License Plates. (Box 54, Folder 11)
  - Standards of Learning. (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - State Building - Eastern Shore. (Box 54, Folder 13-14)
  - State Corporation Commission - Stock/Non-Stock. (Box 54, Folder 15)
  - State Park. (Box 54, Folder 16)
  - Stewardship Act. (Box 54, Folder 17)
  - Stickers/Decals on Windshields. (Box 54, Folder 18)
  - Strobe Lights. (Box 54, Folder 19)
  - Subaqueous Mining. (Box 54, Folder 20)
  - Subaqueous Study. (Box 55, Folder 1-9)
  - Submerged Aquatic Vegetation. (Box 55, Folder 10-11)
  - Substance Abuse Reduction Effort (SABRE)/Red Onion. (Box 56, Folder 1-3)
  - Tangier Seawall. (Box 56, Folder 4-5)
  - Tax Study, 2002. (Box 56, Folder 6-9)
  - Taxes - Health Care. (Box 56, Folder 10)
  - Timber Cruises. (Box 56, Folder 11)
  - Total Maximum Daily Load (TMDL). (Box 56, Folder 12)
  - Transferable Development Rights (TDR's). (Box 56, Folder 13)
  - Transient Occupancy Tax. (Box 56, Folder 14)
  - Transient Occupancy Tax. (Box 57, Folder 1-2)
  - Transportation. (Box 57, Folder 3-4)
  - Transportation - Hampton Roads. (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - Tributary Nutrient Reduction Strategy. (Box 57, Folder 6-10)
  - Tributary Strategy. (Box 57, Folder 11-14)
  - Trucks - Overweight/Liquidated Damages. (Box 57, Folder 15)
  - Truck Lengths. (Box 58, Folder 1-4)
  - Trucks. (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Tulloch Ditching. (Box 58, Folder 6-8)
  - Turning Point. (Box 58, Folder 9)
  - Unemployment Trust Fund. (Box 58, Folder 10-13)
  - Uniform Interstate Family Support Act. (Box 58, Folder 14)
  - United Way. (Box 58, Folder 15)
  - Utility Facilities Construction. (Box 58, Folder 16)
  - Vegetable Board. (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Vegetable Board. (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Vehicle Tax - AAA/CAA. (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - Virginia Alcohol Safety Action Program (VASAP). (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - Virginia Association for Career and Technical Education. (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - Virginia Dental Association - Missions of Mercy. (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - Virginia Eastern Economic Empowerment and Housing Corporation. (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - Virginia Governors Conference, 2002. (Box 59, Folder 7-8)
  - Virginia Health Care Association. (Box 59, Folder 9)
  - Virginia Outdoors Foundation Retirement Plan. (Box 59, Folder 10)
  - Virginia Personnel Act. (Box 59, Folder 11)
  - Virginia Seaside Heritage Program. (Box 59, Folder 12)
  - Virginia State Bar. (Box 59, Folder 13-14)
  - VMRC - Search. (Box 59, Folder 15)
  - VMRC - Stagger Terms of Members. (Box 59, Folder 16)
  - Vodvarka, Joseph J.. (Box 60, Folder 1-2)
  - Wallops Island - Aegis. (Box 60, Folder 3-4)
  - Water. (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - Water Study - Eastern Shore. (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Watermen's Association. (Box 60, Folder 7-9)
  - Watson, Emma. (Box 60, Folder 10)
  - Wetlands. (Box 60, Folder 11-14)
  - Wetlands. (Box 61, Folder 1-2)
  - Wetlands Zoning Boards. (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Wishart's Point. (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - Wishart's Point Harbor. (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Workers' Compensation. (Box 61, Folder 6-8)
  - Workers' Compensation - Second Injury Fund. (Box 61, Folder 9-12)
  - Year 2020 Panel. (Box 62, Folder 1-3)
  - Youth. (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Youth Gangs. (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - Youth Opportunity. (Box 62, Folder 6)
- Series III. Agency Files, 1984-2003., Extent: 9 boxes. (Box 63-71)
  The agency files document Bloxom's dealings with various state government departments, as well as his membership on many boards and commissions, including the Bi-State Blue Crab Advisory Committee, Chesapeake Bay Bridge Tunnel Commuter Toll Impact Study Committee, Chesapeake Bay Commission, Chesapeake Bay Partnership Council, Disability Commission, Governor's Commission on Efficiency in Government, Governor's Commission on Environmental Stewardship, and the Jamestown-Yorktown Foundation.
  - Agriculture/Forestry - National Conference of State Legislatures. (Box 63, Folder 1-2)
  - Bi-State Blud Crab Advisory Committee, 11 December 2000. (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Chesapeake Bay Bridge Tunnel Commuter Toll Impact Study. (Box 63, Folder 4-9)
  - Chesapeake Bay Bridge Tunnel Commuter Toll Impact Study. (Box 64, Folder 1-8)
  - Chesapeake Bay Commission. (Box 65, Folder 1-10)
  - Chesapeake Bay Bridge Commission - Hershey, PA, 2003. (Box 66, Folder 1-2)
  - Chesapeake Bay Partnership Council. (Box 66, Folder 3-11)
  - Chesapeake Bay Partnership Council. (Box 67, Folder 1-3)
  - Community Services Board/Community Action Agency. (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - Commission on Federal Block Grants. (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - Disability Commission. (Box 67, Folder 6-10)
  - Disability Commission. (Box 68, Folder 1-9)
  - DMV/DOT. (Box 68, Folder 10)
  - Eastern Shore Disability Services Board. (Box 68, Folder 11)
  - Environmental Quality. (Box 68, Folder 12)
  - Experiment Station/Cooperative Extension. (Box 69, Folder 1-7)
  - Governor's Commission on Efficiency in Government. (Box 69, Folder 8-11)
  - Governor's Commission on Efficiency in Government. (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - Governor's Commission on Environmental Stewardship. (Box 70, Folder 2-6)
  - Jamestown-Yorktown Foundation. (Box 70, Folder 7-11)
  - Jamestown-Yorktown Foundation. (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - Regional Housing Strategic Plan Advisory Committee. (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - Resource Conservation and Development Council. (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - Small Business Commission. (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - Tangier - Virginia Advisory Legislative Council (VALC). (Box 71, Folder 5-6)
  - Virginia Cooperative Extension. (Box 71, Folder 7)
  - Virginia Employment Commission - Exmore Office. (Box 71, Folder 8)
  - Virginia Information Technologies Agency (VITA). (Box 71, Folder 9)
  - VMRC/VIMS. (Box 71, Folder 10)
  - Virginia Marine Resources Commission. (Box 71, Folder 11-13)
- Series IV. County Files, 1988-2002., Extent: 6 boxes. (Box 72-77)
  The county files contain material on subjects specific to the counties and localities of the 100th District which Bloxom represented. There is correspondence with local officials and civic leaders, legislative agendas and proposals, grant applications and announcements, and other items relating to social services, community and economic development, infrastructure improvements, planning and zoning regulations, environmental issues, and budget and tax matters in a particular locality.
  - Accomack. (Box 72, Folder 1-4)
  - Cape Charles. (Box 72, Folder 5-9)
  - Chincoteague. (Box 72, Folder 10-11)
  - Chincoteague. (Box 73, Folder 1-4)
  - Exmore. (Box 73, Folder 5-6)
  - Gloucester. (Box 73, Folder 7-11)
  - Mathews. (Box 73, Folder 12-14)
  - Mathews. (Box 74, Folder 1-10)
  - Norfolk. (Box 74, Folder 11-14)
  - Norfolk. (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - Northampton. (Box 75, Folder 2-11)
  - Northampton. (Box 76, Folder 1-2)
  - Onancock. (Box 76, Folder 3-4)
  - Saxis. (Box 76, Folder 5-7)
  - Tangier. (Box 76, Folder 8-12)
  - Tangier. (Box 77, Folder 1-4)
  - Wachapreague. (Box 77, Folder 5-6)
- Series V. Reports and Publications, 1981-2003., Extent: 2 boxes. (Box 78-79)
  There are various reports from state and federal agencies, educational institutions, and private organizations in the collection, including the Chesapeake Bay Commission, College of William and Mary, Virginia Department of Conservation and Economic Development, Virginia Department of Mental Health, Mental Retardation, and Substance Abuse Services, Virginia Department of Environmental Quality, Virginia Secretary of Natural Resources, Joint Legislative Audit and Review Commission, National Aeronautics and Space Administration, United States Environmental Protection Agency, and Virginia Polytechnic and State University.
  - Alliance for the Chesapeake Bay. "Baybook: A Guide to Reducing Water Pollution at Home," February 1991. (Box 78)
  - Alliance for the Chesapeake Bay. "Chesapeake White Paper," January 1993. (Box 78)
  - Alliance for the Chesapeake Bay. "Chesapeake White Paper," January 1993. (Box 78)
  - "Chesapeake Bay and Susquehanna River and its Tidal Tributaries: Public Access Guide," 1989. (Box 78)
  - Chesapeake Bay Commission. "The Cost of a Clean Bay: Assessing Funding Needs Throughout the Watershed," January 2003. (Box 78)
  - Chesapeake Bay Commission. "For the Resources: Annual Report 2002.". (Box 78)
  - Chesapeake Bay Commission. "The Introduction of Nonindigenous Species to the Chesapeake Bay Via Ballast Water," 5 January 1995. (Box 78)
  - Chesapeake Bay Commission. "Keeping Our Commitment: Preserving Land in the Chesapeake Watershed," February 2001. (Box 78)
  - Chesapeake Bay Commission. "Taking Action for the Blue Crab: Managing and Protecting the Stock and its Fisheries," January 2001. (Box 78)
  - Chesapeake Bay Local Assistance Department. "Study of the Costs of Complying with the Chesapeake Bay Preservation Act Regulations," February 1992. (Box 78)
  - Chesapeake Bay Preservation Act Program Study Group. "Final Report," July 1992. (Box 78)
  - Chesapeake Executive Council. "Technical Assistance and Incentives to Local Governments," December 1988. (Box 78)
  - College of William and Mary. Virginia Institute of Marine Science. "Manual for Growing Hard Clam Mercenaria," Summer 1984. (Box 78)
  - College of William and Mary. Virginia Institute of Marine Science. "Marine Resources Bulletin," vol. 26, no.1, Spring 1994. (Box 78)
  - College of William and Mary. Virginia Institute of Marine Science. "Proposed Marine Environmental Toxicology/Pathobiology Research Building," 20 September 1989. (Box 78)
  - College of William and Mary. Virginia Institute of Marine Science. "Virginia's Net Fisheries: A Preliminary Economic Overview," 1996. (Box 78)
  - Commonwealth of Virginia. Council on the Environment. "Development Policies and Guidelines," October 1989. (Box 78)
  - Commonwealth of Virginia. Department of Conservation and Economic Development. Division of Parks and Recreation. "The 1984 Virginia Outdoors Plan.". (Box 78)
  - Commonwealth of Virginia. Department of Conservation and Economic Development. Division of Parks and Recreation. "The 1989 Virginia Outdoors Plan.". (Box 78)
  - Commonwealth of Virginia. Department of Economic Development. "Virginia Facts and Figures 1994.". (Box 78)
  - Commonwealth of Virginia. Department of Environmental Quality. "Business and Industry Guide to Environmental Permits in Virginia," July 1993. (Box 78)
  - Commonwealth of Virginia. Department of Environmental Quality. "Business and Industry Guide to Environmental Permits in Virginia," December 1993. (Box 78)
  - Commonwealth of Virginia. Department of Environmental Quality. "Tributary Nutrient Reduction Strategy for the Rappahannock River and Northern Neck Coastal Basins - Legislative Report," 1 December 1999. (Box 78)
  - Commonwealth of Virginia. Department of Environmental Quality. "Virginia's Potomac Basin Tributary Nutrient Reduction Strategy - Draft for Public Review and Comment," August 1995. (Box 78)
  - Commonwealth of Virginia. Department of Environmental Quality. "Virginia's Potomac Basin Tributary Nutrient Reduction Strategy," August 1995. (Box 78)
  - Commonwealth of Virginia. Department of Mental Health, Mental Retardation and Substance Abuse Services. "Comprehensive State Plan, 1998-2004," 11 December 1997. (Box 78)
  - Commonwealth of Virginia. Department of Mental Health, Mental Retardation and Substance Abuse Services. "Comprehensive State Plan, 2002-2008," 30 November 2001. (Box 78)
  - Commonwealth of Virginia. Department of Mental Health, Mental Retardation and Substance Abuse Services. "Report to the Joint Subcommittee Studying the Publicly Funded Mental Health System on Issues Related to Human Rights Protections for Consumers Receiving Services in State Facilities and Community Programs," 14 January 1998. (Box 78)
  - Commonwealth of Virginia. Governor's Commission on Efficiency in Government. "Improving Government Operations: Report on Efficiency and Economy.". (Box 78)